Yuri.
うえはら (上原)百合
Who the hell do you think I am?
なお (菜緒)誰と間違えてんのよ!
Oh my God, he kissed me.
キスしちゃつた…
Me and Uehara...
上原君と
Oh, no...
どうしよう
Hang on,
でもちょっと待って
he thought I was someone else.
上原君は違う人と間違えて キスしたんだよね?
That's it, it's just a mistake.
そうそうそうだよ ちょっとした事故だよね
There's nothing to worry about.
全然気にすることない
No, who am I kidding?
いや気にするよ
It totally worries me.
気になるよ
What should I do?
だって こつ
My very first kiss...
初めてのキ…ス
Because you kicked me,
お前のケリのせいで
my stomach turned red.
俺の腹すげー 赤くなってんだけど
Hey, stay away from me!
(菜緒) もうこっち来ないでよ!
Hey, what's the matter?
仩原) おい何考えてんだよ! !
You're the one who did it, you know.
そっちがあんなこと そつ したからでしょ!
What are you talking about?
仩原)は? 何だよあんなことって
What?
え?
Don't you remember?
覚えてないの?
Remember what?
だから何?
If my alarm's going off, wake me up normally.
っていうか目覚まし鳴ってんなら 普通に起こせよ
-What do you mean normally? -Are you daft?
何よ普通って (上原)だから!
Wake me up gently, OK?
“普通に優しく起こしてください” って言ってんの
There's no way I can do that?
そ…そんなこと できるわけないでしょ!
Hey, you.
あのさ
What?
la...
Don't tell me, after all this time,
今さらながら
you're concerned about living with a boy?
男との同居生活に 危機感覚えたりする?
Are you fantasizing about me making a move on you?
“私襲われたらどうしよう" なんて悶々としてる?
Don't worry.
安心しろ
I have absolutely no interest in you.
俺お前にはカケラも欲情しない
Put my bag back the way it was,
俺のカバン ちゃんと元通りにしとけよ
and like I said before, don't talk to me at school.
あと前にも言ったけど 学校では絶対話しかけんな
Now I'm ticked off.
クソこんちくしょう
Darn him!
何なんだよ
Three meters.
3メートル
Huh? Where did Uehara go?
あれ? 上原君どこ行ったんだろ…
Wait! Where am I?
っていうかここどこ?
Damn, she's so stupid.
やっぱバカだなあいつ
-Good morning. -Hi.
(光石)おはよう まりな)おはよう
Is Nao having the day off today?
(光石)あれ? 菜緒今日休み?
I haven't heard anything. Where is she?
(まりな) とは聞いてないんだけど 何してんだろ?
Today is my big chance to see Uehara.
今日は上原君を間近で見る 絶好のチャンスなのに
So, that's today, huh?
(光石)ああ あれ今日だったか こった
Yep!
(ak 13) TIT
What a load of crap.
(光石)俺は気が重いよ
I got a message from Nao.
あっ菜緒からメール来た
What does it say?
(光石)何て?
She says "I am lost."
"遭難した!”って
What?
(光石)は?
I'm going to be late.
あー遅刻しちゃう
Oh no, it's a dead end.
あっ行き止まり
Help! No!
(菜緒)怖い イヤ!
I had a messed up first kiss from someone
間違えられたファーストキス
who told me he's not interested in me,
欲情しない宣言
and I got chased by a dog!
最後には犬
This is all, completely, entirely,
あれもこれも 全部全部
Uehara's fault!
上原君のせいだー!
Hey! Be quiet in here!
(教師) こら! 校内で奇声を上げるんじゃない
-Yes, Sir! -You are late.
(菜緒)はい (教師)遅刻するぞ
Yes.
(菜緒)はいすいません すいませんすいません…
Aren't you going to eat, Nao?
(まりな)菜緒食べないの?
I think she's run out of energy for today.
1日分のエネルギ 使い果たしたっぽいな こつ
You followed unknown roads, moreover, you have no sense of direction!
方向音痴なのに知らない道 通ったりするからだよ
It's not my fault, it's...
いやそれは 私のせいじゃなくて…
Don't tell anyone we live together.
同居してることも 絶対バラすなよ
Well...
いや…
Actually it's all my fault.
私のせいでございます
Hey, keep your chin up.
(まりな) まあ元気出しなって
After this, we have sports with A class!
午後は待ちに待つたA組との 合同体育なんだから!
Joint sports class...
合同体育...
Hey, come on, you two. Perk up!
ちょっとちょっと テンション低くない?
We can see Uehara who looks so cool!
上原君のかっこいい姿が 目の前で見れるんだよ るんに
I've seen enough. No thanks.
あー私はもういいや 散々見たし
I'm full.
お腹いっぱい 食あたり起こしそう
Come on, Nao, what are you talking about?
何言ってんの 菜緒!
-Get out of the way! -Hey! What the...
みつちゃん邪魔!
-Nao, let's go! -Huh? Why?
(まりな)菜緒 (菜緒)えっえっ えつえつ
-Quickly now! -Wait a sec, Marina!
まりな)早く (菜緒)ちょっとまりな
Look at that. It's like a fantasy world.
見なよ あの現実離れしたルックス
He's so sharp and cool.
はかな 儚げで繊細で
But sometimes, he looks so lonely.
でもね時々 すっごく寂しい顔するの
The shop's sold out of curry bread.
(康太郎) 購買カレーパン売り切れ
Really?
(悠人)マジ!?
Did you see that?
見た!今今!
He's just bummed about the curry--
あつあれは ただカレ
It must be because he suffered while growing up.
やっぱり悲しい 生い立ちのせいだよね
He is the perfect guy for me.
でも憂いを帯びた上原君も またステキ -ステ
You know Uehara lost his parents
(まりな) 上原君ってご両親を幼い時に
when he was a kid, right?
交通事故で亡くしてるじゃん?
I'm no freeloader you know.
俺はすねかじりじゃないからな
So, in conclusion,
(まりな)結論!
no matter how many times I see him,
何万回見ても絶対に飽きない 最高にいい男
he is the perfect man for me! Uehara!
それが上原君なんだよ
Well, I don't like him.
やっぱヤな感じ
-What? -Oh, nothing, don't worry.
まりな)ん? (菜緒)えつあ…何でもない
Don't you think he has a girlfriend?
(菜緒)でもさ上原君って 彼女いるんじゃないの?
Really? Who told you that?
えぇっそうなの!? それ誰情報?
Huh?
あ… め
Yuri.
百合 白合
No, what I meant was that he must have at least one girlfriend.
いや彼女の1人や2人ぐらいは いるんじゃないかなあって よめつ
I haven't heard that rumor yet,
今んところ そういう噂はないけど
but I would be so shocked if he has one.
でもそうだとしたら ショック-
I don't get to see cool guys like him so often, you know?
あんなレベルの高い男 なかなかお目にかかれないのに
I don't know why he's so popular.
っていうか そんなにモテるんだあの人
He is one of the top three.
そりゃ御三家トップだもん
The rules are so tough too.
"掟"も相当シビアだし
Rules?
オキテ…
You heard them the other day.
この間見たでしょ 覚えてないの?
-Remember? -I remember but...
(菜緒)見たけど
The unspoken rules among girls.
(まりな) 女子の間では暗黙の了解なの
Sit.
んっ つ
There are three groups interested in Uehara at the moment.
上原君の取り巻き女子は 今3つの派閥に分かれてるの
First are the teachers' favorites,
(まりな)先生からも 目置かれる優等生女子
Next are the really naughty ones,
悪い遊びをしまくっている アウトロー女子
And the ones that are popular with the guys,
男子から圧倒的人気の マネージャー女子
These three groups decided
この3つの派閥の 女子たちが
to manage all interactions with Uehara.
上原君への抜け駆けは決して 許さないっていう掟を作ったの
Uehara is for everyone.
(まりな) 上原君はみんなの上原君
If you talk with him or meet with him,
不用意に親しくしたり 接触なんてしたら くた
it can cause big trouble!
どんな目に合わされるか
He's like a goddamn national treasure.
もはや国宝だな上原君
Yes, national treasure! No touching!
そう国宝! おさわり厳禁
Hey, shouldn't you be getting ready?
っていうか急がなくていいの?
Next lesson is your favorite, right?
次お前の楽しみにしてる 合同体育だよ
You're right!
(まりな)あつそうだ
Oh, no! I kissed the national treasure!
っていうか私 国宝とキスしちゃってるよ
So, Marina, which group are you in?
(光石)で? まりなはどこの派閥なの?
I'm just one of the majority.
(まり ) 私はその他大勢の1人 な
I just hope that Uehara
いつか上原君が
will approach me on his own.
野に咲く私を 見つけてくれたらいいなあって
Yeah, right. Nice imagination!
(光石) 何かそ 九不毛じゃね?
Mitsuishi!
まりな)みつちゃん... (菜緒)あっ!
-What's up? -What?
どうした? (光石)何?
It's nothing.
いや な…何でもないよ
Nothing at all. I got to go to the toilet.
何でもないから. ごめんちょっとトイレに
I have a sore tummy.
お腹痛い
-Nao?
(まりな)菜緒 (光石)菜緒?
If I get found out...
これを着てしまったら
I'm screwed!
とんでもないことに
Hey Uehara, help us out next lesson.
(翼)上原君次の体育 マジで頼むわ
We don't want to lose to class D.
D組のヤツらには 負けたくないんだよね
No, I'm going to sleep in the infirmary.
いや俺保健室で寝る
Do you know her? She's looking right at you.
(翼)あれ知り合い? すげー見てるけど
Nope, no idea.
いや全く知らない
She's dancing!
嘹平)何か踊ってるよ
Maybe she ate something wrong!
変なもんでも食ったんだろ
You!
何だよ
Hey!
おい
I told you to stay away from me!
ふざけるな 俺に近づくなって言っただろ!
It's an emergency. Read this!
(菜緒)緊急事態なの 読んでよ!
What?
(上原)やだね
Hey, stop it!
(上原)やめろよんっ!
Thanks to her, I couldn't play hooky.
あいつのせいでサボり損ねた
YOSHIKAWA
なつ!
Hey! Wait!
おいおい
You've got the wrong sports clothes, Uehara.
(菜緒) “体操着間違ってるよ 上原くん
There's no one in the home economics room, so let's swap there.
“今家庭科室誰もいないから そこで交換しよう" し”
It's not me, it's your mistake!
間違ったのはお前だろうが!
Hey, wait!
(上原)おい待て!
Stop it!
早まるな!
What the hell? Why did you cut it?
お前…普通切るか?
Because you wouldn't listen to me.
だ…だって上原君が こつ 全然話聞いてくれないから
Fix it!
直せよ
What?
(菜緒)え?
I'll give you five minutes.
あと5分で直せ
That's impossible!
無理だよ!
It's just a small hole.
っていうかほら チロッと穴空いただけだし
It's like wearing a pants with holes in the knees, see?
ほらよく ヒザ擦り切れたりするじゃん?
This is not the knee, you idiot!
ヒザじゃねーだろここは!
There's no shirts with a hole here!
っていうかこんなとこに 穴空いてるヤツいるわけねーだろ
You always get pissed off.
何なのガミガミガミ..
What the...
はあ!?
Fine, I'll fix it.
分かったよ つに 直せばいいんでしょう!
You are such a pain.
うるさいな
If only you had listened to me...
だいたい 話聞いてくれないからじゃん
No, this is your fault,
は?お前が間違えたんだろ
and who the hell cuts shirts like this?
っていうか何だよ この空け方はよ
Can't help it now though.
(菜緒) だってしようがないでしょ こつ
No one cuts it like this though.
仩原)は? こんなとこ切るヤツいねーだろ
Shut up.
(菜緒) うるさいな
Which needle do I use?
もう針どれ? 65針どれ?
Who cares! Use any of them.
(上原)どれじゃなくて どれでもいいよ
I found it.
(菜緒)あつあつた つめつた
Not yet?
まだかよ
Don't rush me, OK?
焦らせないでよ
Hurry up. You are a girl, right?
とやれよ 一応女だろ
Hey, that's a stereotype!
そういうのね そつ 偏見って言うんだよ
You were going to sleep in the infirmary anyway.
どうせ サボろうとしてただけでしょ
That has nothing to do with it.
それとこれとは話が別だ
What a pain in the ass.
面倒くさっ
What did you say?
何か言った?
No, nothing.
いえ何にも
Ouch!
イッタ… ツ
Oh, are you OK?
おい大丈夫か?
What the hell? It's no big deal.
何だよ大したことねーな
Hey, come on,
何その言い方
what would you do if a girl got a scar on her hand?
女の子の手に傷でも残ったら どうすんですか?
A girl?
女の子?
If you're a girl, fix this!
女の子ならこんぐらいやれよ
Shut up, I'm doing it now.
うるさいな やってんじゃん今
-You are taking forever. -Help me then.
全然進んでねーじゃんかよ (菜緒) じゃ手伝って 云つ 一手
Strike three! Batter out!
(教師)ストライク! バッターアウト
-Do your best! -You can do it!
(声援)
Strike! Batter out!
(教師)ストライク! バッターアウト
-Uehara, you're so cool! -You're awesome!
(女子生徒)上原君かっこいい
Don't worry about it, Mitsuichi.
ドンマイ!みつちゃん
It's only you coming for me, Nao.
菜緒だけだよ 俺を迎えてくれるのは
-Don't say that, it's not true. -Yes, it is.
そんなことないよ (光石)そんなことあるよ
-Nao! -Hi, Daichi.
(大地)菜緒
-Do you have sports class too, Daichi? -Yeah.
(光石)大地先輩も体育ですか? (大地)おお
Hey, you are holding the bat wrong.
お前バットの持ち方が 全然なってない
Daichi, can you teach me?
(菜緒)大ちゃん 私に教えて!
I want to hit him for a home run!
私あいつから ホームラン打ちたいの
-At any cost... -Wow, that's not like you, Nao.
何が何でも 休地ハッ珍しいな
You're all feisty.
菜緒がそんな 闘争心むき出しなんて
I don't like him.
だって何か こつ ヤな感じじゃない?
-Just because he's cool, -You're right.
ちょっとかっこいいからってさ (光石)そうだそうだ
good at sports and doing well in school,
(菜緒)スポーツができて 勉強ができるからって
-he thinks he can get away with anything. -That's right.
何でも許されると思うなよ! (光石)そうだそうだ!
The world doesn't revolve around you!
全部が自分中心に回ってると 思ったら大間違いだ!
Yeah! Not you!
そうだそうだ!
-Hit it! -I will.
打菜緖)打つ (菜緒)打つ
-Nao, you will hit a home run! -Yep, I will!
菜緒はホームランを打てる
First, this is how you hold the bat.
じゃあまずは バットの持ち方から
OK!
(菜緒)はい
Don't try to hit it with your bat, use your whole body.
でボールが来たら バットで打つっていうよりかは
Like a spring, unwind and hit!
重心移動して体で打つ
Strike!
(教師)ストライク!
Three Strikes! Batter Out!
(教師)スリーストライク! バッターアウト
Game Over!
(歓声) (教師)試合終了!
What? That's it?
え?ウソ もう終わり?
Uehara could have gone a bit easy on me.
上原君少しぐらい 手加減してくれたっていいじゃん こつ
Huh? Where is my uniform?
(菜緒)え?あれ? あれ?私の制服…
Yoshikawa.
よしかわ (詩織)吉川さん
This was on the hallway floor. Is it yours?
これ廊下に落ちてたけど 吉川さんのじゃない?
What? Did you drop your uniform, Nao?
ええ!?菜緒 制服落としたの?
Perhaps... Thank you.
ああ...そうかも ごめんありがとう
Hey, what's wrong with you?
ちょっと何してんの?
Maybe this is all part of
(美南)でもそういう 隙があるところが
Yoshikawa's charm?
吉川さんの魅力なんじゃない?
I'm so jealous of her feminine charms.
(エリカ)羨ましいわー 女子力高いって
Looks like Uehara is interested in you as well.
上原君も吉川さんには 目置いてるみたいだものね
What? Really?
えっそうなの!?
No, not at all.
そんな...
-Bye then. -See you around.
渼南) ゃお先に (エリカ) またね じ
Milk pudding or milk jelly...
でもさー 牛乳プリンと牛乳寒天
It's so hard to choose between them.
どっちか選ぶの 本当迷っちゃうんだよね
It's such a tough choice.
もう究極の選択だよね
I love the richness of pudding,
もうあのプリンの濃厚な感じ 魅力の1つなんだけど
but I also love the smoothness of jelly.
あの寒天のツルンとした感じが もうたまらないんだよね
Which do you like better, Marina?
のつねえ まりなどっち派?
-What are you hiding? -What?
何隠してんの? (菜緒)え?
Whenever you hide things,
菜緒隠し事ある時って
you talk a whole bunch of crap, over and over.
どうでもいいこと ペラペラしゃべるじゃん
Really?
いや…
I didn't mean to babble.
どうでもいい話 してるつもりじゃ…
Wait, Marina!
(菜緒)ちょっとまりな
Now, Marina...
あのねまりな
What the hell?
こういうこと?
You're living with a boy like this?
こういう感じで男と 同棲しちゃってますってこと?
It will take a bit to explain, but...
あのね話は長くなるんだけど
You were hiding it from me too?
私にも秘密にしてたんだ
Sorry.
ごめん
That's the whole story.
(菜緒) ...というわけ
So we're not living together nor dating.
(菜緒)だから同棲とか 付き合ってるってわけじゃなくて
I'm just waiting until a space is available in the girls dorm.
女子寮が空くまでは 我慢って感じ
So, who is it?
で誰?
What?
え?
The guy you are living with?
その一緒に暮らしてる男
Well, it's...
あ~それは
Older, same age? Which one?
年上?タメ?どっち?
About the same, I think.
同じくらい…かなあ? フフフッ
What? Same school? Do I know him?
マジ!?同じ学校とか? 私知ってる人だったりする? こった
What? Daichi?
あ! まさかの大ちゃん?
Not him, no.
なわけないか
No, not him.
うんないないない
So, better than him? Worse?
じゃあさじゃあさ レベル的にもっと上?下?
Definitely worse... I mean Daichi is one of the top three.
ってそりゃ下だよね 大ちゃん御三家だし
Well... I'm not sure.
上?かな…
What?
え?
Socially, he's actually above Daichi.
大ちゃんより上みたい 世間的には...
Which means that...
フッそれってもうさ
It's Uehara!
上原君じゃん!
Welcome home.
お…おかえり
I thought you have part time job today.
今日バイト早いね
I finished early.
今日早上がり
Oh, I see.
あ…そうなんだ
This is my best friend, Marina.
あつこちら親友のまりな
Of all days, why today...
もう何で今日に限って
Go.
(まりな)んっ
Darn it all!
ん-もう!
Sorry that I kept it a secret.
秘密にしてて本当ごめん!
Nao!
菜緒
Yes?
(菜緒)はい
This is amazing!
まりな)でかした (菜緒)へ?
Sit down, sit down.
ちょっと座って座って
This is so amazing.
だってだって あの上原君と
If I come to your house,
菜緒んちにくれば
I can meet him anytime, right?
必然的に上原君にも 会えるってことでしょ?
Well, I guess yes,
うんまあ...
but he is usually at work, not home.
でもバイトで ほぼ家にいないけど
So, Nao, how do you feel about him?
菜緒はどう思ってんの?
About what?
何が?
You don't feel anything for Uehara?
上原君のこと 何とも思ってないの?
Nothing actually.
うん 思ってないけど
Really?
本当?
Nothing at all.
うん全然
If that's the case, can you help me? Please! Set me up with him!
じゃあ協力して で仲取り持って お願い!
I guess I can try,
まあ別にいいけど
but Uehara is not the guy you think he is.
でも上原君 まりなが思ってるような人じゃ.
You're not even listening.
って聞いてないし
Oh, what? Yay!
えつあつイエーイ!
Yay!
TI-T...
-See you then. -OK, see you tomorrow.
(まりな)バイバーイ (菜緒) またねバイバーイ
I don't understand why she likes him so much.
(菜緒)あれのどこが そんないいんだろ...
Crap, you scared me!
おっ!びっくりした
He didn't hear me, did he?
バレてないよね
Hey!
おい
What do you mean?
何って?
Living together. If we get found out, we'll be expelled!
同居 バレたら退学だぞ
I know--
(菜緒)分かってるよ (上原)分かってねえから
Listen to me--
ちょっとそんな言い方
Keep her quiet, OK?
ちゃんと言っとけよ 絶対言いふらすなって 小 よつ
Marina's not like that.
まりなはそんなこと する子じゃないから
-How do you know? -I just know.
何で分かんだよ (菜緒)分かるよ よる
She's been my friend since junior high.
まりなは 中学ん時から友達だし
Friend...
友達ね
What do you mean?
何よ
I can't trust her.
ますます信用できねーな
What?
は?
Your friends are just like you. Totally absent minded.
お前の友達なんかお前同様 ボケボケに決まってんだろ
Hey, you!
お前な!
Marina is
まりなは
totally different from me.
私とは全然違うの
She's serious and strong. You don't have to worry about her!
しっかりしてて絶対大丈夫!
You don't even know Marina, but you say you don't trust her.
まりなのこと ちゃんと知らないくせに
That's not fair.
おかしいよそんなの
Marina is a friend I trust the most!
まりなは私が一番信頼できる 友達なんだから!
What a complete jerk!
すっごくすっごくヤなヤツ!
I hate you!
もう大っ嫌い!
What the fuck?
わつわっ!
Where are you going?
どこ行くの?
The toilet.
トイレ
Yoshikawa, what are you doing?
(教師)吉川さん! 何してるの?
I'm so sorry.
(菜緒)はいごめんなさい
Nao, are you OK?
まりな)菜緒大丈夫?
Yeah.
(菜緒) うん
Really?
本当に?
What?
(菜緒)え?
Something's up this morning.
何か今日朝から変
You're not yourself.
元気ないし
Oh!
あっ!
Did something happen with Uehara?
もしかして昨日 上原君と何があった? つに
No, that's not it.
え?ううん
I'm just a bit hungry. That's all.
ちょっとお腹すいただけだから
-Really? -Yes, really.
(まりな)本当に? (菜緒) うん本当
When you are not smiling, it really upsets me, you know.
菜緒が笑 と つてない 私も調子狂うんだからね
Thanks, Marina.
ありがとうまりな
No problem.
ううん よいしよ
Oh, dear...
あ~あ
Yoshikawa, someone's calling for you.
(康太郎)吉川 お前呼ばれてるってよ
Who?
えっ誰が?
Uehara. He's waiting in the PE hall.
(悠人)上原君 体育倉庫で待ってるって
Really? Thanks.
そっか ありがとう
Maybe she's really popular?
慷太郎)あいつ実は モテてんのかな?
-Well... -Huh?
(悠人) つ よつ (康太郎)おう な
Why would he call for me at school?
何で急に 学校で呼び出すんだろう
What did I do wrong this time?
私また 何かやらかした?
Uehara?
上原君?
Where is he?
あれ?どこ行った 1丁つた...
What?
ゲ...
Sorry, we tricked you.
ごめんなさい ウソついちゃいました
There's no escape, you know.
渼南) 逃げらんないんだからね
So, what is it between you and Uehara?
(エリカ) っていうかさ あんた上原君の何?
What?
(菜緒)何って
Stop pretending, spit it out!
すっとぼけんのも 大概にしなさい!
Don't pretend that you don't know
ひさし (美南)上原久志の掟
the rules about Uehara Hisashi.
知らないとは言わせないわよ
Hey, why are you here, Uehara?
あれ?上原君 何でここにいんの?
What?
え?
Uehara is for everyone, OK?
(詩織) 上原君はみんなの上原君なの
You got it?
分かった? (エリカ) っていうかあんたは
She's right.
(美南)確かに
I'm amazed you have the guts to meet Uehara with that face and body.
よくそんな貧相な顔と体で あの上原君の前にいられるね
Even though he is so cool and perfect,
(詩織)全てが完璧でクールで
he has a big scar on his heart.
なのに心に悲しい傷を 負ってしまった悲劇の主人公
-That is Uehara. -Poor Uehara.
(詩織)それが上原君なの (美南)かわいそうな上原君
But we all are always by his side.
でも私たちはずっと 上原君のそばにいる
We're kindly watching over him.
上原君のことを 温かく見守り続けることが
That is our reason for living.
私たちの使命なの
-That's right. -Yep, she's right.
(3人)だよね そうだよね
He absolutely needs us.
私たちが必要不可欠っていうか
You're so right.
そうそれだよね
I don't think he needs that.
そういうのいらないと思う
-Huh?
は?
He's not poor Uehara, you know.
上原君は かわいそうなんかじゃないから
He doesn't need you.
(菜緒)そんなのいらない
Huh? What are you saying?
渼南)は? (詩織)何言ってんのよ ?言 は何
-Uehara lost his parents-- -I know!
上原君はご両親を (菜緒)知ってるよ
I know that,
知ってるけど
but when someone is doing his best,
でもいろいろ 頑張ってる人には
you should say, well done, not poor you, right?
“かわいそう”じゃなくて “すごいね”でしよ!
Your rules are so stupid.
そもそも“掟"自体が おかしいんだよ
-Huh?
(3人)はあ!?
You keep saying you know him
さっきから見た目とか雰囲気で
because of his looks and this and that,
上原君のこと ああだこうだ言ってるけどさ
but if you really want to get to know someone,
本当に相手のこと 知りたいんだったら
You should talk, laugh and fight with him.
もっと話したり 笑ったりケンカしたり つに
Without doing that, how could you know?
そういうの繰り返さなきゃ 分かるわけないじゃん!
For those who don't even know that,
そんなのも 分かんないダメ女子には
Uehara won't even express the slightest interest!
上原君は は欲情しないから! カケラも
Oh, dear, I said it all.
全部言っちゃつた つに
Right, now you've pissed me off.
(菜緒)キャッ! ーき ッ頭 ヤか キ何 緒南 菜美
Who the fuck are you?
つうか何様なんだよ お前
Fuck off.
クソムカつく
-Uehara?
(4人)上原君!?
You, you are just so stupid.
お前ってさやっぱアホだな
What?
なっ... なつ...
She is my girlfriend.
こいつ俺と付き合ってるから
Huh?
え?
When you have a problem, tell me.
(上原) 文句があるなら俺に言えよ
-No way... -You're lying.
(詩織)ウソウソ (美南)そんな
Uehara?
(エリカ) う…上原君
Let's go.
帰るぞ
Hey...
あ…あのさ
What?
何?
Why are you doing this?
何でこんなに なつちやったんだっけ?
Me and you--
私と上原君ってさ
Be quiet. Just walk, OK?
いいから 黙ってサクサク歩け
OK.
はい
Oh my God!
(女子生徒たちのざわめき)
Nao?
菜緒?
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
No one's looking now, right?
ここまでくれば 誰も見てないだろ
What?
え?
I thought it over again.
(上原) よくよく考えたらさ
I realized pretending to be strangers was impossible.
まるっきり他人のフリっていうのは 無理があるよな
If we pretend to go out, I have a reason to go to your house, right?
付き合ってることにしとけば 家に行くのも不自然じゃないし
So, what you're saying is...
それってつまり
Let's pretend to be going out.
付き合ってるフリしようぜ
Pretend?
フリ?
Oh, sorry, did I get your hopes up?
あつごめん 期待させちゃつた?
No, not really.
別に…してないし
OK, so you want to really go out then?
何なら本当に付き合う?
Got you!
ウッソー
Well, I've got to go to work. Bye.
じゃあ俺 このままバイト行くから
Uehara,
上原君
thank you
ありがとう
for saving me.
助けてくれて
I'm sorry.
悪かったな
Huh?
ん?
About yesterday.
(上原)昨日
About your friend.
あんたの友達のこと
Oh, that... yeah.
あ…うん
Go back quickly or you'll catch a cold!
早く帰んねーと風邪ひくぞ
Okay.
うん
Uehara?
上原君?
Uehara!
上原君
Hey, are you OK?
ねえ上原君 どうしたの?
Hey, Uehara...
ちょっと
Don't worry, he's just tired from work and not enough sleep.
(医師)心配ないですよ 疲労と睡眠不足
Maybe he was just a bit undernourished.
あとは軽い栄養失調が 重なったかな よつたかな
If he eats properly, and rests for a few days, he'll be fine.
2~3日ゆっくり休んで ちゃんと食べれば大丈夫
Thank you so much.
はいありがとうございます
I've gotten in touch with his family too.
(医師)一応彼のご家族にも 連絡しておいたから
Take care.
お大事にね
Uehara?
(菜緒)上原君
Oh.
おお
"Oh?" I was really worried about you.
"おお,じゃないよ すっごい心配したんだからね
It's because you sleep on the couch.
もうソファでなんかで 寝るからだよ
You're exaggerating, it's nothing.
(上原)大げさなんだよ これくらいで
Nothing?
これくらいって
Right, let's go home.
よし帰るか
What?
え?
Hey, take it easy.
ちょっとそんなのダメに 決まってるでしょ!
I'll be fine if I eat something yummy.
俺の体は うまいもん食えば治る
What?
は?
Yuri.
百合 白合
Yuri?
(菜緒)百合って。
So she's Uehara's girlfriend?
この人が上原君の?